Krunal Bhavsar

Pancham Blossom, B/S. Shree Siddhnath Planet, New Karelibaug, Vadodara, Gujarat 390018

+91 - 8000656437

in http://linkedin.com/in/krunal-bhavsar-2743b275

Profile

Junior Php Developer with 1.6 years of experience in the Technology domain looking for a development position. Supportive and enthusiastic team player dedicated to efficiently resolving project issues. Ability and willingness to innovate and learn new technologies, quick learner passionate about development.

Skills

Backend Technologies

Php, Laravel, My SQL, OOPS

Git

GitHub, Mange Repository

Tools

VS Code, Xampp, Tortoise Git, Slack

Frontend Technologies

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap

Project Deployment

Web Hosting, Mange Domain-Subdomain, Mange Web Mail,

Other

WordPress, C, C++, ASP.NET, C#, Java, VB

Work Experience

07/2021 – Present Vadodara, India	Sanfinity Creative Solution Pvt. Ltd., Junior Php Developer
03/2021 – 06/2021 Vadodara, India	Sanfinity Creative Solution Pvt. Ltd., Trainee

Projects

OTSPL, Website

Dynamic website which providing Supply Chain Solutions, Transportation & Logistics Services worldwide. URL: https://myots.sanfinity.in/

Gururaj Engineers, Website

Dynamic website which providing industrial automation solutions of products and specializes in Thyristor DC drives; Torque Motor Controllers, Vibrator Feeder Controllers, Timers, Pulse Jet Timers, SSRs, Ratio Cards, ZSRs, Solid State Heating Panels, PLC Based Systems, Custom Built Equipments, other Machine Dedicated Controls, etc.

URL: https://gururaj.sanfinity.in/

Pranav Plastic, ERP

Web application of customized ERP for master module to generate order book to dispatch and etc. URL: http://pranavplastic.sanfinity.in/

IEC Engneering, Website

Dynamic website which providing engineering solutions and industries for supply of pumps, couplings and motors.

URL: https://sanfinity.in/iec_engg/public/

Umiya Enterprise, Website

Dynamic website which providing manufacturing and engineering solution, manufacturing of high-pressure vessels such as Autoclaves, Condensers and Heat Exchanger from Stainless Steel and Mild Steel. URL: http://umiyasteelfabricators.com/

JD Visa Services, Website

Dynamic website which providing visa consultancy services, study abroad, immigration, tours and travels and Test preparation.

URL: http://jdvisaservices.com/

GDS Harni, Website

Dynamic website for School which providing education, organizing events and other services.

URL: https://www.gdsharni.com/

Natraj Enterprise, Website

Static website which providing Supply of Motors, Generators & Alternators.

URL: http://natrajenterprise.co.in/

Robotechfuture, Web Application

Web application of lead management system for robotechfuture product trading indicators and services, etc.

URL: http://sanfinity.in/robotechfuture/public/

Electech Power, Website

Dynamic website which providing Electrical solution and Manufacturing and Supplying of Control Panels, PCC Panels, MCC Panels, APFC Panels, Distribution Boards, Testing Panels, etc.

URL: https://electechpower.com/

Pavilion Heights, Web Application

Web application of lead management system for real estate project.

URL: https://sanfinity.in/pavilion/public/

Sanfinity Group, Website

Company's dynamic website which providing group of companies and services.

URL: http://sanfinitygroup.com/

The Sanfinity, Website

Company's dynamic website which providing different kind of services.

URL: https://thesanfinity.com/

The LTPL, Website

Dynamic website which providing warehousing, shipping, logistics, marketing and consultancy services, trading in B2B and B2C segment.

URL: https://www.theltpl.com/

News1click, WordPress Blog

News blogging website.

Sanfinity CS, Website

Company's website for providing consultancy services.

URL: http://sanfinitycs.com/

OTSPL, Web Application

Web application for freight forwarding system.

URL: https://otspl.co.in/

Awards

23/06/2021	Awarded Employee of the Quarter & Promotion, CEO
Education	
08/2020 – Present Vadodara, India	Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology, Sigma Institute of Engineering
08/2009 – 07/2012 Vadodara, India	Diploma Engineering in Information Technology, Parul Institute of Engineering & Technology (PPI)
Languages	

Languages

English, Hindi, Gujarati

Interests

Playing Cricket, Tabla and Musical Instruments, Listening Soft Songs & Music, Singinig